[DE]  Hi and welcome or welcome back. My name is Millie and my channel is all about finding comfort in video games.
Hi and welcome or welcome back. My name is Millie and my channel is all about finding comfort in video games.
[DE]  In this series we work on a Minecraft forever world. I have to say it's very slow paced and I usually find myself chatting about whatever is on my mind.
In this series we work on a Minecraft forever world. I have to say it's very slow paced and I usually find myself chatting about whatever is on my mind.
[DE]  But I hope this serves as some background noise whilst you get stuff done, be it your own game, some work, or studying, or even to fall asleep.
But I hope this serves as some background noise whilst you get stuff done, be it your own game, some work, or studying, or even to fall asleep.
[DE]  So I hope you'll join me whilst I make some progress.
So I hope you'll join me whilst I make some progress.
[DE]  And yeah, let's begin.
And yeah, let's begin.
[DE]  And we start today with the sun going down.
And we start today with the sun going down.
[DE]  It's a very quick sunset.
It's a very quick sunset.
[DE]  The sounding of the horn is to mark the arrival of the moon.
The sounding of the horn is to mark the arrival of the moon.
[DE]  It's actually a very traditional sort of process in this village.
It's actually a very traditional sort of process in this village.
[DE]  And uh, yeah let's head to uh, head to bed.
And uh, yeah let's head to uh, head to bed.
[DE]  Oh.
Oh.
[DE]  Oh, I- I didn't realise this was a... a hostel.
Oh, I- I didn't realise this was a... a hostel.
[DE]  I thought this was my house.
I thought this was my house.
[DE]  I hope you can like clip through the wall.
I hope you can like clip through the wall.
[DE]  His nose is too big to clip sleeping with the horn horn He not really getting the memo so just push him off
His nose is too big to clip sleeping with the horn horn He not really getting the memo so just push him off
[DE]  He instantly claimed it as soon as I got up. That's very rude. You guys are...
He instantly claimed it as soon as I got up. That's very rude. You guys are...
[DE]  The rules are you have to leave. Now did I come to their village and take the house?
The rules are you have to leave. Now did I come to their village and take the house?
[DE]  Yes, but I think I remember it being empty when I got here so... A bunny. It's
Yes, but I think I remember it being empty when I got here so... A bunny. It's
[DE]  probably my favorite colorway for the bunnies and as tempting as it is to take
probably my favorite colorway for the bunnies and as tempting as it is to take
[DE]  this rabbit. I can't do it. I can't have pets until I have some building done. Things are
this rabbit. I can't do it. I can't have pets until I have some building done. Things are
[DE]  more settled. And I really have no idea where to start in terms of building. I guess the
more settled. And I really have no idea where to start in terms of building. I guess the
[DE]  nether portal's over there. See I thought the cherry grove was kind of one whole island,
nether portal's over there. See I thought the cherry grove was kind of one whole island,
[DE]  But there are two cherry groves.
But there are two cherry groves.
[DE]  It's sort of, it's a much bigger island in the middle.
It's sort of, it's a much bigger island in the middle.
[DE]  Okay, I wonder if I can get over there just by jumping into the water.
Okay, I wonder if I can get over there just by jumping into the water.
[DE]  Now it looks steep, but I think there are many blocks in between one of these edges
Now it looks steep, but I think there are many blocks in between one of these edges
[DE]  in the water.
in the water.